<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoodWill</string>
    <string name="button_finddriend">Looking for a friend</string>
    <string name="button_takefriend">Take the friend away</string>
    <string name="welcome">What is GOODWIIL?</string>
    <string name="button_help">Whom do we help</string>
    <string name="button_feed">To Feed</string>
    <string name="cost">What is the value of your like?</string>
    <string name="button_buy">Buy it</string>
    <string name="you_buy">You have already purchased</string>
    <string name="offer">You want to buy :</string>
    <string name="slide4_button">To Start</string>
    <string name="prit">Shelters</string>
    <string name="share">Share on FB</string>
    <string name="info_about">Reports</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">Every day people spend their spare time in social networks from 1 up to 6 hours. The bigger part of this time they spend liking other people photos.</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">What are these infinite likes? The most important question is: what is the benefit for you and others of these likes?</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">At GOODWILL everyone simply can help homeless animals by liking.</string>
    <string name="slide4_tt">HOW DOES IT WORK?</string>
    <string name="slide4_tts">5 steps to help:</string>
    <string name="slide4_pt1_descr">GO TO THE FEED SECTION</string>
    <string name="slide4_pt2_descr">CHOOSE THE VALUE OF YOUR LIKE</string>
    <string name="slide4_pt3_descr">LIKE EVERYTHING YOU ARE EAGER TO PURCHASE FOR ANIMALS * You can buy products by yourself or with your friend</string>
    <string name="slide4_pt4_descr">PAY WITH YOUR CARD VIA GOOGLE PAY *The remaining funds are automatically transferred to the general needs of shelter</string>
    <string name="slide4_pt5_descr">WEEKLY RECEIVE A REPORT ABOUT YOUR HELP</string>
    <string name="act_photo_1">DON\'T SAVE THE DOGS. SAVE HUMAN.\nIN YOURSELF.</string>
    <string name="info_1">A STORY THAT DOES NOT LEAVE ANYBODY</string>
    <string name="info_2">LEATHER DRESSING</string>
    <string name="info_22">" IS IN THE PAST, WHEN THERE HAS BEEN 60 YEARS OF TORTURING ANIMALS"</string>
    <string name="info_3">THE FIRST INCOME OF $ 10,000 WAS MADE BY BRIZHIT BORDO</string>
    <string name="info_43">THERE ARE MUCH NON-BUSINESS PEOPLE. ARE WE, UKRAINIANS, APATHETIC?</string>
    <string name="info_4">PEOPLE KNOW ABOUT THIS SHELTER</string>
    <string name="info_42">ALL OVER THE WORLD.</string>
    <string name="info_5">"LET’S CHANGE THIS "</string>
    <string name="info_51">TENDENCY TOGETHER?</string>
    <string name="info_6">A SOS SHELTER,</string>
    <string name="info_61">" IN WHICH TODAY"</string>
    <string name="info_62">" 1000 DOGS "</string>
    <string name="info_63">AND 300 CATS HAVE NESTED</string>
    <string name="info_64">For details on the link:</string>
    <string name="instruction1">Found your tailed friend?</string>
    <string name="zvit1">How many tailed friends recovered? How many dogs and cats have you fed? How many fluffies have found their home?</string>
    <string name="zvit2">For details on the link:</string>
    <string name="next">Back</string>
    <string name="donate_descr">If you want to make</string>
    <string name="donate_descr1">"a donation for "</string>
    <string name="donate_descr2">the general needs</string>
    <string name="donate_descr3">"of the shelter:"</string>
    <string name="donate_descr_pt1">ENTER THE AMOUNT YOU WANT TO DONATE</string>
    <string name="donate_descr_pt2">CARD PAYMENT</string>
    <string name="donate_descr_pt3">LOOK REPORT IN YOUR PERSONAL ACCOUNT</string>
    <string name="nointernet">&#160;&#160;&#160;Sorry you dont have internet connection!\\n&#160;&#160; Please connect to internet and open GOODWILL again.</string>
    <string name="title_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="title_like">Shop</string>
    <string name="title_about">About</string>
    <string name="button_back">Back</string>
    <string name="you">You :</string>
    <string name="sb1">Hi! My name is Palkan, I am a courageous and at the same time gentle guy. I am about 4–5 years old. I dream of a family and a house that I can adequately protect. In the meantime, my owner is looking for me, sometimes I miss. However, I have many friends, so the time for sadness is not enough.</string>
    <string name="sb2">Hello! My name is Sultan. I\'m about 3–4 years old. I do not know why they called me that. As for me, I do not look like a sultan at all. Perhaps because I, like a real man, everywhere I feel most important?</string>
    <string name="sb3">Hi! My name is Svetka. I have such a popular Ukrainian name so that everyone can easily remember. I do not know how old I am, but in my heart I always remain a little girl. And yet, all the girls envy me through my eyes. Do you see how well they summed up little black?</string>
    <string name="sb4">Hey there! I\'m still quite small and I have no name yet. But it\'s cool, because you can call me to your taste. I have a little nose, and also beautiful eyes. Let\'s be friends?</string>
    <string name="sb5">Hi! I really like to play hide and seek. I tried to hide from the camera, but for some reason they found me so quickly. I\'m still quite small and I have no name yet, but I am very soft and kind. Perhaps, I am your future friend? </string>
    <string name="sb6">Good time of the day! I love to be photographed. From this photo shoot I have sooo many photos. If you like to be photographed for social networks - we already have something that unites with you. Below you can meet my sister, she is more shy.</string>
    <string name="sb7">Hi! I am a girl and I want to handle. Although I am still quite small, but I already know how to be friends sincerely. Perhaps you are my friend?</string>
    <string name="sb8">Hey! I do not have a name, but I often hear in my address such words - “fluffy”, “lohmastik.” At first, I was embarrassed about my fluffiness, but now I realized that this was my peculiarity. I am a very dedicated dog. I welcome all the guests of the shelter, and then accompany them to the car itself.</string>
    <string name="sb9">Hi! I am very playful and cheerful dog. Three more puppies live in the shelter with me. We are a gang, which with joy and love meets everyone who comes to visit us.</string>
    <string name="sb10">Hi! If you are looking for such a beautiful cat like me, tips for our acquaintance! I do not know how old I am, but I\'m still that tough nut.</string>
    <string name="ata">Total :</string>
    <string name="atall">Total : 0 uah</string>
    <string name="empty">Your cart is empty</string>
    <string name="button_friend">Invite a friend</string>
    <string name="allready">You have already purchased</string>
    <string name="meet">Meet</string>
    <string name="about_pr">ABOUT SHELTER</string>
    <string name="info_12">COLD...</string>
    <string name="about_string">- a world where your likes and time spent on them will finally be useful</string>
    <string name="about2">We understood that help should be targeted and understandable to all. So we came up with help curses, because the speech likes today is clear to everyone.</string>
    <string name="about1">GOODWILL is a socially responsible initiative, which aims to house the homeless animals to always be fed and in heat.</string>
    <string name="instruction2">- call us</string>
    <string name="instruction21">You can :</string>
    <string name="instruction3">"- go to address, city Kyiv Pyrogivsky shlah st., 186 "</string>
    <string name="clear_cart">Clear cart</string>
    <string name="whoweare">About</string>
    <string name="yourlike_1">Choose and start shopping</string>
    <string name="donate_sum">Enter amount</string>
    <string name="change_like">Change like cost</string>
    <string name="you_can_change">You can always change like cost in your Profile</string>
    <string name="write_labl">- write</string>
</resources>